megasets.com 2015-11-09

# DomainsDeal.com

[Home](http://domainsdeal.com/index.php) _ _ Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy and the personal information you provide us is a top priority at DomainsDeal.com . For this reason, DomainsDeal does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent or in way other than as outlined in this privacy policy. At DomainsDeal, we want our users to fully understand what information we collect, how we use this information, and the steps we take to protect your personal information. 

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for DomainsDeal.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website. 

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
